Ganesh Narawade WEB DEVELOPER

PHONE: 021 02458501

EMAIL: ganesh9211@hotmail.com

PORTFOLIO https://ganesh9211-dev.github.io/portfolio/

Visa Status: NZ Permanent Resident

GITHUB: https://github.com/ganesh9211-dev

Summary

I am a highly motivated, full stack web developer with a passion for software development and learning. I embrace challenges, offer diverse experiences and am an agile learner. I have just completed Industry Connect boot camp which gave me 300 hours of a simulated work environment, where I developed several apps. I am excited to bring my positive attitude of making clients happy from my hospitality background, to the tech world.

Skill Highlights

TECHNICAL:

- Web Development
- User Interface design
- Application Support
- JavaScript (ES6), React.js
- HTML5, CSS3
- Bootstrap
- Node JS, NPM
- RESTful APIs
- SQL databases
- Git, GitHub

PERSONAL:

- Team player In my previous career, I have been part of diverse teams where team work was paramount.
- Problem Solving I love problem solving and code error finding, I always check logically about errors and deep dive into it to sort it out.
- Fast learner Learned how to build complex designs for my personal projects in a short amount of time.
- Works well under pressure A skill I perfected during my time in the fast-paced environment in the hospitality industry e.g. handled 4 big functions at one time.
- Professional Communication In my previous work environment,good communication was the key asset to have as I had to handle customer requirements professionally e.g. dealing with French rugby team management.

Experience

Portfolio

https://ganesh9211-dev.github.io/portfolio

Full Stack .Net Developer (Intern) MVP Studios, Wellington

March 2019 - August 2019

Talent-Onboarding Project

Worked as a full stack developer for the Talent project, front end was on ReactJS and Webpack, hosted on Azure.

- Learned full stack web development technologies, including front-end frameworks and SQL databases.
- Attended and contributed to the daily scrums and strategizing the workflow according to the project.
- Introduced state management to the team.
- Writing services for API's (C#, Net)
- Designing the Ul's for the web using React and SemanticUI (bootstrap library for react)
- Gained experience with web technologies such as C# web services architecture, front end technologies (React, Webpack), introduced state management to the team to re-designed the parts of front end and modified services, learned and implemented Agile and SCRUM methodologies.

Conference & Events Supervisor

March 2015 - March 2020

The Rydges Hotel, Wellington

- Efficiency in planning and organising various events and ensure customer satisfaction.
- Assist and direct the team to ensure a high level of service is executed. Strong attention to details.
- Make rosters, order beverages & linen, also plan for the future events.
- Work with Accounting department to track payment to all vendors & service providers.
- Own the planning and delivery for all front of house aspects of the event.
- Actively ensure customer satisfaction through direct interaction with customers
- Generate revenue & wage cost report & send it to Food and beverage Manager on daily basis.
- Proficient working knowledge of computers, Microsoft Excel, Word and Outlook.
- Resolving inter-departmental & staff conflicts.

Food & Beverage Supervisor (Restaurant & Conference)	September 2013 – March 2015
Abel Tasman Hotel, Wellington	

Food & Beverage Supervisor (Restaurant & Conference)	December 2010 – September 2013
The Rydges Hotel, Wellington	

Food & Beverage Attendant (Fine Dine Restaurant)	October 2010 – March 2011
White House Restaurant, Wellington	

Food & Beverage Attendant (5 star luxury hotel)	January 2010 – June 2010
The Grand Hyatt Mumbai, India	

Food & Beverage Attendant (4 star deluxe hotel)	April 2009 – December 2009
Parabola Restaurant, Rodas Mumbai, India	·

Food & Beverage Attendant (4 star hotel)	October 2006 – October 2008
The Rembrandt Hotel London, UK	

Education

React.js Course	CODE ACADEMY	2020 – 2020
JavaScript for beginners' basics Course	Mosh Courses	2020 – 2020
Software Development Boot Camp course	INDUTRY CONNECT	2018 - 2019
Bachelor of Hospitality Management degree (level -7)	Wellington Institute of Technology (WelTec) 2010 - 2011
Hospitality Management -Postgraduate Diploma	London school of Business and Computing	2007 - 2008
Hospitality Management -Advanced Diploma	London school of Business and Computing	2006 - 2007
Twin Diploma in Hospitality Management	Rizvi college of Hotel Management	2003 - 2005
References		

References

Lakhan DeshPande from LPS New Zealand Sarabh Sathe from SKYCITY Entertainment Group

Email: deshpandelakhan@gmail.com Email: saurya271@gmail.com Mobile no- 022 303 4554 Mobile no- 0210 313 586